<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Zodiac Symbols RecyclerView</string>

    <!-- create an arrays for zodiac names and dates -->

    <string-array name="zodiac_name">
        <item>Capricorn</item>
        <item>Aquarius</item>
        <item>Pisces</item>
        <item>Aries</item>
        <item>Taurus</item>
        <item>Gemini</item>
        <item>Cancer</item>
        <item>Leo</item>
        <item>Virgo</item>
        <item>Libra</item>
        <item>Scorpio</item>
        <item>Sagittarius</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="zodiac_dates">
        <item>Dec 22 - Jan 19</item>
        <item>Jan 20 - Feb 18</item>
        <item>Feb 19 - Mar 20</item>
        <item>Mar 21 - Apr 19</item>
        <item>Apr 20 - May 20</item>
        <item>May 21 - Jun 20</item>
        <item>Jun 21 - Jul 22</item>
        <item>Jul 23 - Aug 22</item>
        <item>Aug 23 - Sep 22</item>
        <item>Sep 23 - Oct 22</item>
        <item>Oct 23 - Nov 21</item>
        <item>Nov 22 - Dec 21</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="zodiac_description">
        <item>Smart, hardworking, and fully in control of their destiny,Capricorn signs will always get what they set their mind to,in both personal and professional life—no excuses.Capricorns may get a reputation as stubborn, but they simply know what they want,and also know how they wish other people would behave.</item>
        <item>Independent and enigmatical, Aquarians are unique.
            There is no one quite like an Aquarius, and because each is so incredibly individual,
            it can be tough to describe them as a group.</item>
        <item>Smart, creative, and deeply intuitive,
            Pisces can be close to psychic. Pisces feel things deeply, and have incredibly strong gut reactions.
            A Pisces knows things from deep within, and can often judge whether
            a person or situation is good or bad.</item>
        <item>The first sign of the Zodiac, Aries are the trailblazers.
            Passionate and independent, Aries will never do something just because
            everyone else is doing it a Ram
            needs to be 100 percent committed to the task at hand.</item>
        <item>Smart, ambitious, and trustworthy, Taurus is the anchor of the Zodiac.
            Amazing friends, colleagues, and partners,
            Taureans value honesty above all else and are proud that their personal
            relationships tend to be drama free. </item>
        <item>Smart, passionate, and dynamic, Gemini is characterized by the Twins,
            Castor and Pollux, and is known for having two different sides they can display to the world.
            Expert communicators, Gemini is the chameleon of the Zodiac, adept at blending into different groups
            based on the vibe and energy they perceive. </item>
        <item>Emotional, intuitive, and practically psychic;
            ruled by the moon and characterized by the crab, Cancer has so much going on in its watery depths.
            Cancer signs may seem prickly and standoffish at first meeting,
            once they make the decision to become friends with someone,
            that person has a friend for life.</item>
        <item>Bold, intelligent, warm, and courageous, fire sign Leo is a natural leader of the Zodiac,
            ready to blaze a trail, vanquish injustice, and make a name for themselves along the way.
            Blessed with high self-esteem,
            Lions know that they possess enviable traits—and they are proud of them.</item>
        <item>Smart, sophisticated, and kind, Virgo gets the job done without complaining.
            Virgos are amazing friends, always there to lend a hand and also lend advice.
            Practical Virgos are incredibly adept at big picture thinking,
            and planning out their life, their vacations,
            and what they are going to do today is not a drag it makes them feel in control and secure.</item>
        <item>Intelligent, kind, and always willing to put others before themselves,
            Libras value harmony in all forms. Ruled by Venus, the planet of beauty,
            Libra adores a life that looks good.
            As the master of compromise and diplomacy, Libra is adept at seeing all points of view,
            and excels at crafting compromises and effecting mediation between others.</item>
        <item>Passionate, independent, and unafraid to blaze their own trail no matter what others think,
            Scorpio signs make a statement wherever they go. They love debates, are not afraid of controversy,
            and wont back down from a debate. </item>
        <item>Independent and strong-willed, Sagittarius personalities are all about going off the beaten path.Sagittarius is not afraid to step away from the pack,and is a natural born leader who goes after what he or she wants,regardless of what other people think.Sagittarius is a born adventurer, and loves solo travel and exploration.</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>